Hello, everyone.
Hi, everyone.
Today, I'm not going to talk about the clothing part.
We are going to talk about making something interesting.
But if you really want to learn the clothing production,
you still have to follow our official MD account
and watch Cherry's videos.
I'm Cherry, not Cherry.
I'm crying.
Because I used to have a colleague named Cherry.
And then someone kept calling us.
Okay.
I'm crying.
This is...
Cherry, right?
And then she usually shares a lot of tutorials.
And then sometimes when I'm studying, I'll go and take a look.
And then the content I'm going to share with you today is...
Hello.
And then we'll combine them together to create an effect.
And then we'll first...
Maybe about the MD part,
and then...
Not too much.
And then we'll talk about some GSP,
and then there's some OC rendering stuff.
And then we'll find a model first.
I'm going to put a little photo in there,
and then,
we'll see what happens.
So we're done with the first step,
and then we're going to go in and look at the code.
And then we're going to go back
and see what happens.
Okay?
So...
What I wanted to say was,
I think my
first impression of the project in the community
was that,
you know,
Then there is a shoe model here, and then we are now in the first step is now in the CCB, and then you this shoe for him to simply open the needle and then let him have a from the top to the bottom of a slowly falling effect.
And then before we do this, we're going to deal with this model first, because if your model.
He has some piercings or faces that are too much, too much, and then when it's simulated in MD, his version will have piercings with the model and then it's not easy to adjust.
So we're going to do this.
Just a simple one like this.
Let him fall.
That's all.
And then we can get out.
Yes.
Thank you.
Teacher Zhu is like Yiyang qianxi.
That's my photo.
And today, before the live broadcast, teacher Zhu told me, I think there are fewer people who don't know Yiyang Qianxi in China, and then I was dumbfounded at the time.
I don't know what kind of person YiYangQianXi looks like.
Now we can start the expansion effect.
When we do the expansion effect,
we can also talk about it.
A friend of mine asked me a question.
If you have any questions, please reply to me.
I have some questions.
He asked me how to make pleated clothes
more delicate and delicate.
We can also talk about it in this case.
In fact, after the update of MD10,
I saw that there was a pleated dress in it.
The designer of the pleated dress did a good job.
If you are interested,
you can research the clothes provided in MD10
when you are free.
If the condition allows,
you can do the same as me.
Just take off my wife's clothes
and study them.
Yes.
I saw your post the other day.
I was looking at the circle of friends.
I saw your post.
I thought
the sense of belonging is too strong.
It's already in my fist.
Sometimes,
when you encounter some pieces of clothing
that you don't know how to make,
you can't find the picture on the Internet.
The people who don't know how to make clothes
can't find the picture on the internet.
The person who can't find the picture on the Internet
is the person who has no idea what to do with it.
They don't know what to do with it.
They just don't know how to do it.
You can't do it.
You have to find out what to do with it.
Just look at the picture on the Internet.
You can do it.
Why can't you find it?
You can't.
I can't.
I'm not sure.
I think
it's not that easy.
Hello, hello, can you guys see my screen?
The internet is blowing up
Oh my god
Oh no
Wait, let me turn off my screen
Let me reconnect
My internet is blowing up
Hello, hello, can you guys hear me?
Hello, hello
The internet is blowing up
Hello, hello, can you guys hear me?
Ok, ok
Let me try and talk to the uv株
I am going to have to talk to the uv株
Hello, hello
Oh, ok
It's back again
I don't even know why the internet is blowing up
Hello, can you guys hear me?
Yes, I can
Sorry, my internet is blowing up
It should be okay now.
Oh, I suddenly realized that I forgot to turn on the live stream.
Let me set it up.
Oh, it should be okay now.
It should be okay now.
Is it okay now?
Yes, it is.
Sorry.
I was wondering why we were watching the cat here.
It turned out that I didn't turn on the live stream.
Let's continue.
After setting the pressure for the two boards separately,
turn off the gravity first.
Turn off the gravity first.
Then turn these two boards down a little bit.
The first thing I need to do is to click on the button.
Click on it.
Wow, it's so flexible.
It looks like it.
I'm going to lock it here to prevent it from floating when I do the simulation.
Then we can make it look like two band-aids.
This part is actually drawing the board and adding pressure, right?
There is no other change, right?
Yes.
Now you can see this.
It's very равowness.
It has no problem with the feels.
It looks not too well and good to see.
We can do some setting.
Let's try reducing namaj burgers boilingOn the board a little bit.
And then we're going to do this inside the seam line and then we're going to add a elasticity
As you can see, after adding the elasticity, then it's going to have a little bit of a shrinkage and it's going to have a little bit of a fold
Because at this point in time, we're actually only going to have a 10 on this board
When we put the other part on the back
And then we're going to take the shoulder of the board
If you make it a little bit smaller, it's going to be a little bit more delicate and it's going to look more real
At this point, we can put it right here and we're going to freeze it and we're going to make two simple
The bag
What about this
So there if you are
Time to just forget it
So I'm going to try to do this
besondue
em
I'm going to make it
Do the thing
It's the same as the video on youtube
well
You can edit the baby
Are you scolding me?
Compared to the clothes, it's much easier to make this thing.
But it can also provide you with a whole new idea.
MD can not only make clothes,
but also use it for its simulation.
MD is excellent in the field of cloth and dynamic simulation.
So we can use it to make other things.
It can not only make clothes.
Wow, this is such an embarrassing description of MD.
When people ask me how I make MD,
I can only say it's very easy to use.
It smells good and it's very easy to use.
What happened?
Why did you dim your light?
Oh, the thing I'm most afraid of has finally happened.
There was a bug during the demonstration.
Why is there no response to this simulation?
Let's try to recreate it.
Have you ever changed the weight of something like this?
No, right?
Oh, you said I remembered.
I think I just turned off the weight.
Oh.
Hmm.
I remembered when you mentioned it.
Yeah, because I feel like you should have done something to the weight.
That's why it's like this.
Okay.
I've been talking about other things and I forgot about this thing.
What do you mean?
I just remembered.
I forgot to turn the AC off.
Yeah, because I forgot to turn off the AC.
I forgot to turn it on.
Look at this.
This is my favourite game.
I've never played this kind of game before.
Oh.
I feel so sorry for you.
I'm just looking at this through the internet.
Yes, I think if you want to use MD, you still have to keep thinking about how to use these functions
It's not a very limited function
Because I used to do something in MD, like lighting up lights
Because I'm not like everyone else in the 3D industry
Or in the clothing industry
So I usually try to do things that I can do in MD
I won't do it in other software
Unless it's something that I can't do in MD
Yes, I agree
I think some of the videos that you updated before were very impressive
Because sometimes, in most cases
Like some small parts
I will put them in other 3D software
And then I see that you can complete a whole set of clothing and accessories in MD
I admire you
The main reason is that I don't use other 3D software
So every time
I just
Have to force myself to do it
Just do it in MD
Just do it
Yes, when I saw it, I thought it was awesome
Just like I see you can do it in other 3D software
I can't do it myself
Like this kind of complicated stuff
I can only
Just call Jimmy
Jimmy, can you do this?
Jimmy, can you do this for us?
Anyway, we...
We have a new colleague
And he has a 3D background
It's very useful
Jimmy is really useful
Just praise Jimmy
Yes, in fact, you can do more related things in MD
It's not just clothes
Some other things can be done
And then for these two versions
You can give him a little bit more
Can you change his hair?
And then
Change his braids
Make him feel more comfortable
Oh
Oh, so now I know
Why did you give him a needle?
I just didn't understand
Why did you give him a needle
This is...
This is the
Yes, indeed
I always forget about it.
And then, we can change the size of this expanding object.
We can change the size of this expanding object.
And refresh the grid.
Sometimes, when we use AMD to make clothes,
especially for those expanding clothes,
in order to get better results,
we need to make the scale very small.
At this time, it's very laggy and easy to break.
Wow, do we need to show how to reduce the number of particles?
Actually, the reason I make the scale very small
is because it's easier to use AMD to make clothes.
I saw a comment saying that
Jimmy is a fat guy.
This is the truth.
Jimmy is a new staff.
Do you think he dares to say bad things about me?
Do you think he dares?
Do you think he dares to say bad things about you?
In the beginning, I used AMD to make clothes,
This is because in other 3D software, if you do some kind of dynamic fabric simulation,
the process is very, very slow and requires baking.
The other thing is that its load effect may not be as ideal,
but it is very convenient to use MD in MD to do this kind of expansion effect.
After this is done,
you can simulate the action.
Wow, that's awesome.
You can do this?
No, you haven't used it.
You must have used this function before.
I used to use it in Bilibili,
but I didn't know that there was a software called MD.
Then I saw a lot of people doing that kind of dance video of MMD.
They should be using this function, right?
Oh, you said I used this animation.
If your needle is not...
Is your needle okay like this?
Wait a minute.
In this case, this bag will get more and more expensive.
I forgot to delete it.
I didn't expect that the shoes can remove this thing.
We have experienced professional training.
I can't stop anymore.
It's usually good to pull it back in the animation.
We have experienced professional training.
We can't laugh unless we can't help it.
We can't sit and talk at the same time.
After the simulation,
the time will go back to normal.
I don't think I've ever encountered this.
It's normal.
And I didn't encounter this problem when I tested it before.
Do you want to send me an email?
Send me a project file.
Send it to my mailbox.
I will read it.
Don't affect the speed.
Sorry.
Women will only affect the speed of my pulling.
It fell out again.
Do you want to increase the friction?
I think it will be fine if I increase the friction.
I used the simulation before.
If I go back directly,
its model is always
not moving with it.
So every time I finish the simulation,
if there is a problem,
I will fall back again.
Really?
I don't think I've ever encountered this.
Where to send an email?
Sherry at MarvelousDesigner.com
Let Jamie send me an email.
I always accidentally
use my own
own
own own
own own own
own
There is a bug, the new function...
No, the new function, there is a bug in the new version
And then this bug is fixed
The pudding version will be that
Okay, the bag plus the layer is okay
But it's like this
Because it's now this
The bottom of the version
Is the hair line
Is the bottom is the inner layer towards the outside
If you want to set the layer
You have to set a surface flip first
MD 10 individual version
280 yuan, is it the price of one year?
Ah, no, it's a month
Sorry
Our price is a bit expensive
How about the bag year?
The bag year will be cheaper
And if you are a student
You will have a discount
Rejection is also too...
It's okay
I just pretend that I didn't see this chat
We have a free trial version
For the first month
MD 10 has a free trial version
Everyone remember
To get it
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Oh, I feel like this time he might have succeeded.
The silence is tonight's counter.
Why isn't it moving again?
A strange half increase.
What?
The comments said to use GPU.
Ah, using CPU is also possible.
It's easier to have these strange things with GPU.
How about setting the friction to a higher value?
Is it possible to set the friction to a higher value?
I feel that friction is really...
You can try to.
In the details element.
And if the friction is not good,
then...
It will be very awkward
MD, is it a year of peace? Isn't it a buy-off?
Uh, it's not a buy-off anymore
Um, how do we adjust this line?
Uh, why don't we just freeze the other panels
And then change its shrink rate to 100
And then let it flow out
And then wait for it to stabilize and then change it back
Um
And then if you set a layer, it should be able to flow out
Is the previous buy-off still updated?
Updated
First of all, you can convert the previous buy-off into a year of peace
Oh, if it doesn't flow out, you can turn the bottom layer over
Change its pressure to positive
And then try it
Oh, hahaha
And then not only this one has a problem
The one just next to it also has a problem
Forget it, I'll...
I'll think about it and adjust it
Okay
Take your time, it's okay
Today is a happy Friday
There's still a lot of time
Thank you
I thank you
well
Roll over
I have to do this
great
It's so tough
I feel bad
it's so ask
Follow on Facebook
Live on Facebook
Fortunately, no comment is on you is not not long
Why don't you just control him directly?
otherwise
Now
I'm getting more and more nervous.
Really?
It's okay, it's okay.
If you can't do it, you can just open a project file.
Let's just pretend that this has never happened before.
They are perfect.
This is what they look like when they are simulated in AMD.
When I was doing it myself,
I really didn't encounter this problem.
It was pretty smooth.
Yeah, sometimes when I do it myself,
I also encounter all kinds of problems.
So when I'm doing a live stream,
I usually don't do live shows.
Because live shows are the most nerve-wracking.
I keep thinking about what to do.
Yeah, life is always different.
I still remember one time,
I went out to a company for a live show.
And at that time,
I didn't know why my computer...
Anyway, as soon as I looked at the screen,
the clothes started to shake.
As soon as I looked at the screen,
Then I...
Then we have a meme here.
It's called the network cause.
No matter what problem you encounter,
you just say, it's the network cause.
It's the network cause.
Then I looked at the clothes at that time,
and then I said,
it might be the network cause.
I don't know why,
but now,
this look...
It looks like a...
a bittersweet feeling of being in a bikini.
A strange illusion appeared.
It feels like...
A strange illusion appears.
I'm in a bikini.
I don't know why
but it looks like a bikini.
My face feels like a bikini now.
What's that?
A little bittersweet feeling?
It's like this.
Well,
I think it feels like a bikini.
I don't know what that means,
but it feels like a bikini.
It must be...
It must be like a bikini.
A very, very,
very strange feeling.
What is it?
Let's go ahead and show off.
It's okay, I think we still have a lot of time.
We can wait a bit longer.
Let's adjust this.
Okay, let's just do it like this.
Even though these two bags don't look very good.
It's okay, life is like this.
Life is always meaningless at the beginning.
I think the world above is not that big.
So...?
I think this bag is too big for me.
It's not that big for me.
What do you mean by big?
I'm not saying it's too big for you.
You are my friend.
You know, I'm not saying it's too big for me.
I'm saying this is pretty cool.
I don't think this is the best place for it to be.
This is my good friend.
The world below us is like this.
You are my friend.
The world below is like this.
I'm going to lock it, and then we're going to bring this in.
会有回放的。
肚子饿了。
哎呀。
外卖快点。
我今天晚上因为在家里面做直播,所以想说等做完直播之后再吃东西吧。
我怕叫外卖,然后不知道什么时候她就突然按门铃,然后直播的时候就听到一阵叮叮叮叮叮叮叮叮。
一看这个说外卖少吃还是自己做饭快乐的人。
你没有在我们群里面。
我们群里面的人都知道我做饭会把厨房炸穿的。
我就只能吃外卖,我自己不能做饭。
但是只有会做饭的人才会说。
说自己做挺好。
像我这种不会做饭的人。
而且你们每天做饭上班累不累?
大家都是打工人,本来就已经很累了。
Oh, no, I love MD the most. Every day when I go to work, I'm so excited, so happy, so full of energy every day.
Zhu Zhu, what are you doing now?
Are you adjusting the lighting?
I'm adjusting the lighting.
Yes, because...
Since I couldn't reach my ideal state when I was adjusting the lighting,
I started to feel more nervous.
Yes.
Don't be nervous.
I think he looks okay now.
Is MD always familiar in Korea?
I remember the first time I went to the headquarters,
I felt like there were people I didn't know around me,
and I couldn't get used to eating.
Then,
if I use the new version of OC,
the lighting will be removed.
Now we have two lights for the model.
The second light is from the back of the object.
The position of the back of the body,
and then the outline of the object.
At the same time, it will also form some light on the background.
Then we can set a background.
This is a layer.
Then we can remove this light.
Change the path of this light to 2.
Then remove the 2 from this label.
Then this light will not work on the background.
Then let's color the background first.
I'll give you a solution.
The right person and the right quality.
The context.
So,
we're going to take a look at what happened to this part.
One is this.
The other is this.
It's not.
All of them,
except that this part is a fake.
It's not the face.
The whole thing is性.
The whole thing is the face.
It's just not the face.
If you look at the whole thing,
the one that has no teeth was the lead.
This is the preferred part.
It's not that.
I'm gonna try to do the same.
That's why this thing's so ugly.
There's only one.
There's two legs.
There's a tongue.
So let's open it up and see what's inside.
Let's see.
Let me change the color of the light.
Let me change the color of the light a little bit.
Oh!
I was just playing around.
After that,
let's give the background a light again.
Turn off the light,
but the camera is visible.
I'll turn it on for the moment.
I'll make sure it's fixed.
I've adjusted the color.
It's been fixed.
Let's make it dark.
Let's make the background dark.
I'm going to make a white line first.
I'm not going to make something like this.
I'm going to make it dark.
Let's do it a little darker.
I'm going to make it darker.
The first one is the best.
I'll make it like this,
but I'll get bad.
I'll give you the last one.
I'll make it dark.
I'll keep that somewhere else.
Isn't the color too dark?
I think it's okay.
Can I make this gray?
I'll let you do it too.
Okay.
Let's make it white.
It's my first time doing this.
It's probably harder.
Then the basic light of the model is ready, and then we can put the material on it.
There seems to be more presentation in terms of C4D and OC than in terms of MD.
No, the presentation in terms of MD is actually quite long.
Because of MD, there are some problems.
It takes a long time to delay.
It's okay.
Actually, this idea is quite special.
Because I haven't thought about it.
I think it can be combined with animation.
In the end, it will become a silent thing.
I usually use animation to change the movements and things like that.
And then this shoe, make it a more retro-looking color.
Not for me.
But I want to make it a little more retro-looking.
It's a little more to the touch.
You can't really see it, can you?
It's not in the right place.
It's too different.
This is too much.
It's too much.
I like this.
Good.
There's a live stream, there's a live stream
The comments are very interesting, ah, not very interesting, but it's very interesting to shoot mp
No, you're not wrong, I'm a lot more
The comments are asking, what graphics card did you use?
My graphics card is 3080
That's good, you've left a tear of envy
I just finished my computer this year, and then I didn't, and then...
Then the third season came out, it's really good
I'm going to update the graphics card
This texture density looks like it's okay, so I don't have to adjust it
I'll just write it like this
And then we'll give it a color
Teacher Zhu, how do you visualize these ideas?
It's a very abstract question.
Tell us what it is.
Do you want me to tell you a story?
Have you ever had a nightmare about a baby?
No.
I feel like I'm starting to get the hang of it.
Yes, I feel like I'm getting the hang of it.
Everyone has come back.
Wow, what this comment says,
this is called concentration.
Or I should still switch back to the voice of the male Xueli, which sounds more normal, doesn't it?
Oh, oh, what step has Mr. Zhu taken now?
Is Mr. Zhu this example? Why is it called Mr. Zhu?
Is the name tag on the shoes made by C4D?
The name tag on the shoes is made by a model.
Oh, I see.
There was a question about the name tag of the MD.
My own work.
Let's take a look.
My favorite part of watching works.
This one.
This kind of name tag is usually made in MD, and then it turns out to be a model.
It's an OBG model, and it has a lot of faces, and it can't be misplaced.
If you use MD to make a name tag, you can only do this.
But if you combine other software like SP or those that can be used to make stickers, this can be done with hair.
So I tried to improve the hair.
If you have a wide range of hair,
You can also do a lot of image editing.
But I think it's best to just use a model.
You can use the model as a model, and then the image will be made.
You can also make the appearance.
Maybe it's not that convenient to make hair.
It's not the time.
It's fine if you don't have a styler.
But I want to make it.
It doesn't have to be done on the head.
I usually do this kind of cloth material or some fur material, it is all a little bit of a drop, so it's best to give it a little bit when it's colored
I'm going to use this one. Is this one not enough? How many do you want?
I'm going to use this one. Is this one not enough? How many do you want? How many do you want?
It slipped, it slipped. No, you can leave it for a little bit longer
And why are you called Mr. Xia?
I used to be called Mr. Xia
I use your WeChat for a long time, so I always watch who this name is
braeraeraeraeraeraeraeraeraeraeraeraeraeraeraeraeraeraera a
How to dye your hair?
how to dye your hair?
how to dye your hair
How come there are still people asking about Chloe?
This is Motherless Designer
I don't know if my Chloe colleagues are watching
Hurry up and take this person away
Is there a picture?
Bilibili can't send pictures
Otherwise, there is a picture
I use MD's official account to return
Chloe's official account to collect the ones we don't know
and send the screenshot
If you ask Chloe,
Chloe's rendering is V-Ray rendering
That's right, hair is usually
rendered in other 3D software
If you are interested,
I can share with you some of my weird outfits
Wow, that's great
Do you know?
My Chloe colleagues
When I showed your work to my Chloe colleagues
They all said that you did a good job
The clothes are very colorful and elegant
The design is also very interesting
When I heard that the design can be shared
I suddenly woke up
I came back and woke up
Wow, that's great
But in fact, those versions
It looks very simple
I didn't make it very complicated when I made it myself
Most of them are just like the one I made just now
Most of them are
Let her
Slowly simulate herself
And then she adjusts it constantly
This is a strong person, brothers
I'm sorry
I cut it back
Wow, is this a strong person?
Strong people say
Oh, I made this very simple
Very convenient
Not tired
Just like when I was in high school
Those students with good grades in the class
They will say
The exam
Oh, it's not hard
I don't review when I go home
homework
I finished my homework at school
I go home and watch TV
I watch TV at night until 10 o'clock
Sleep on time
Indeed, this is what the big brothers say
You sleep at night
Sleep on time
No, I don't
I don't
Oh my God
I don't like this
I always feel like writing in my unconsciousness
I feel like the color combination is getting more and more colorful
I just left it on a whole gray shoe
At that time, I was thinking that this is straight male beauty
Then suddenly it suddenly became beautiful
Actually, it was also very beautiful before
That is called
It's called
Pure
Now it's getting chubby
It's like Timo's hat
You can think of the League of Legends
Because you want Timo, right?
The original painting of Timo is green, yellow, blue
Then the red mouth
This is Timo's shoes
Yes, the color combination is pretty good
But the color combination is really
It will take a long time to do the project
When I do clothes
I'm most afraid of the color combination
I usually match several sets
Then let my colleagues choose
Which one looks better
I choose the one with more
I will use that as the last one
Use this live broadcast
There is an online chat
Ask you
Teacher Zhu, what brand of display do you use?
Color changes
Display color
My display is LG
I saw a comment asking which brand to use for the color adjustment, which brand to use for the color adjustment.
Well, the problem is that I saw a picture on Weibo saying that the designer is at the end of the day, and then I put a picture of all kinds of mobile phones and all kinds of computer screens and the color difference of the same picture came out.
I feel that the sense of代入 is too strong and it's starting to sweat.
I didn't pay attention to this. Is there a big difference between their different brands?
There is a big difference between the color of the phone screen and the color of the phone screen, so I don't think it's a matter of one person.
In fact, the most important thing is to ask Jiafeng, if Jiafeng tells you that I want your orange, can you light it up a little more, can you blush it a little more, and the picture I gave you doesn't seem to be the same.
I said, oh, okay, can you say it more accurately, it's the same as my picture, I said, oh, well, sometimes I say it's the color of the straw, but it seems to be a little different, and I said, oh, okay, I'm tired.
This is the same thing I say.
Let's make it a little bit more realistic.
Let's make it a little more realistic.
The black box is a little too real.
the black box is a little too real.
What else? Can you make that D raid?
Well, what?
It's getting bigger and smaller overall.
It's getting smaller and smaller.
All right, here we go.
Here we go.
And that's about it.
I'm going to show you the whole thing.
I think that's about it.
Yeah!
Happy shout from the workers.
That's awesome.
That's really good.
And then let's take a look at the version.
All right, all right.
Wow, that's too heartless.
Just drag it to the replay station in public?
That's really too heartless.
I'm going to cry.
Which version do you guys want to see?
I've made a lot.
Wow, it's so pretty.
Just look at it.
Have to watch the rap show.
This is so beautiful.
Wow, there's really a lot.
How can you imagine this kind of dress?
This is what I think.
I think it's very difficult.
Everyone is the same.
This kind of costume, if you create it,
there are no rules or versions.
Just do whatever you want to do.
And then just keep imitating it.
And then look at its status.
And then finally choose one that you think looks comfortable.
It's a satisfactory effect.
Wow.
If you look at the inside,
I think it's pretty simple.
There's almost nothing like that.
There are a lot of curves.
Or there's a very neat one.
There's a very neat one.
It's all made by some 004-year-olds.
But I think it's pretty fun to make this kind of thing.
Wow.
I think they're all strong people.
You see.
Actually, this Gogigo is all positive and all straight-shaped.
How can't it come out?
I think I…
But when it comes to the clothes,
this Gogo's dress is very light.
It feels like there's a lot of curves.
Actually, all the dresses are straight-shaped.
They're all the same ones I just explained.
I tried it, but I couldn't do anything about it.
The simulation speed was too slow.
I think it was around 7 or 6.
But the results were pretty good.
Wow, that's really impressive.
But there was a lot of pressure,
and there were a lot of bigger versions.
I think it would be harder for me to get to 5.
Yeah, if I only made a few versions,
and the clothes were simple,
I would probably get to 5 or 5.
Once you have a lot,
it's pretty painful to try.
The computer is constantly showing progress.
Wow, I'm crying.
I feel like I've been doing this for so many years,
and I'm doing it for nothing.
Forget it.
Look at the 2D version.
It looks very messy.
All kinds of messy stuff.
There's a recording.
If you open this version and share it with everyone,
I think they won't be able to learn anything.
Then why did you suggest
that I take these versions out
and show them to everyone?
That would be bad.
No, it's just that
someone asked me,
and I was very curious.
He said,
I want to see your version.
I said,
it looks weird when I see your clothes.
It's very abstract.
I just want to see what the version looks like.
As you can see,
the version is...
It's very boring.
How can you just say it plainly?
It's not that special.
Anyway, you won't learn anything if you see it.
Forget it.
You won't learn anything if you see it.
When I say it myself,
I think it sounds pretty normal.
But when you repeat it,
I feel like it sounds...
It's not that good.
Maybe it's because
sometimes when I say it plainly,
it sounds a little dull.
It's because of the smell.
So...
If I repeat it,
it sounds a little dull.
This one is even more broken.
Oh my god.
It's very interesting
how MZ expands.
You can try it.
If you make a lot of clothes,
and you think you can change it,
you can try this.
Change it?
What is this?
This is...
a red cat unit.
It's so magical.
I admire it.
It's a big brain.
So,
the main thing is
Mr.Zhuzhu's
personal presentation.
It's not really related to
whether you can learn it or not.
Even if you watch this version,
you can cover the 3D window
on the left side of the screen,
and I can't even figure out
what kind of clothes I should make.
There was a question I collected before.
It's about making a belt.
That student asked me,
is the belt made in MD,
or is it made in CCD?
Generally,
when I make a belt,
in MD,
I only make a vertical waist
with a plate,
and then
I make a belt buckle
in CCD.
In MD,
there is also a belt buckle
provided in MD,
but it's relatively simple.
If you want to make
some more rich effects,
I go to CCD
and rebuild it again.
If you want to increase your speed,
you can just make a belt buckle
on the side of the screen.
If you want to make a belt buckle,
you can make a belt buckle
on the side of the screen.
It's from a friend.
He asked me that
if I want to make
a belt buckle
on the side of the screen,
I can also do that,
but...
if it's not in thety,
you can make a belt buckle
You can arrange the position.
But you can't learn anything from this version, because it's very messy.
And you may not be able to use it to make some changes,
and then change it to another style.
I think it's pretty good to be able to put it together.
If I want to put it together,
I may have to sew it to the right-hand side of the sewing line.
And this kind of three-dimensional design is also made by MD.
It's really good.
So I summed up the technical points of Mr. Zhu Zhu.
It is to rely on the brain.
There are no technical points.
This may be the difference between an artist and an ordinary person.
I am that poor ordinary person.
Open MD at work every day,
find clothes,
and then make the version honestly.
And the artists,
they can make all kinds of clothes.
This is the difference.
I can't do the technical flow.
So I can only do some subtle things.
I admire the technical flow very much.
Teacher,
your creativity
where does it come from?
It's just that usually,
if it's to collect creativity,
you can go to Pinterest or Behance.
And then,
if you want to make more interesting clothes,
you can also pay attention to some fashion releases,
especially like the one in Chuanjiubaoling.
Oh,
right.
Sometimes,
when I make clothes,
I also look at the fashion releases.
I especially like to look at their clothes.
And then open MD,
find myself,
oh,
I can't do it.
Forget it.
Just turn it off.
Yeah,
just turn it off.
Forget it.
Don't do this.
It's too formal.
Too formal.
Look at the comments.
Any questions?
My friends,
when I see the comments,
it feels like we all come in and chat.
Hum.
Wow.
Well,
it feels really good.
My mind is particularly big.
Ah.
Why do you have so much time to make so many clothes?
I'm a freelance designer. I don't go to work. I stay at home every day.
I like to stay at home and don't go out much.
I sit in front of the computer and keep creating.
It's so fun.
I'm a workaholic.
I like MD the most. I go to work every day.
I really like to go to work.
I don't like staying at home at all.
This is what I was going to show you today.
I'm so sorry that I turned it upside down during the live stream.
It's a small problem. Just pretend you didn't see it.
This is the finished product.
But is there any other picture?
There is a icon on it.
I see the inflatable shoes.
The inflatable shoes next to it.
It seems to be normal before.
The inflatable shoes are made of fabric.
This is not made of MD.
Oh, really?
Yes.
So you can make two versions.
One is made of MD and the other is molded.
Yes.
I think it looks more natural and softer with MD.
This looks more like plastic or foam.
It looks strange.
It looks like plastic foam.
I think the shoes like this are more like in real life.
I'm sure it's made of plastic foam.
This is more artistic.
And the finished product looks like something that's obviously made of cotton.
This is also very cute.
The color matching is cute.
Let's see if there are any questions in the chat
Why is it so late?
There's a pineapple
Is this pineapple rice ball the one they were talking about?
There's a pineapple rice ball
Oh, so it's you
I'm so happy to see you
There were a lot of comments about you
Saying that I have a friend named pineapple
This pineapple wants a project file
Huh?
So it's really you
I thought it was the comment that said the person wanted the file
The person wanted it
It turned out that it was you who wanted it
That's great
I also want a blank
I'm envious
Let's see if there are any more comments
Questions
Little friends, are there any more questions?
If there are no more questions, then we can
Do you guys understand my hint?
Oh, I still want to see the work
All right
Is bubble material a sticker?
Bubble material
Bubble material is not a sticker
It's a strip
How do you hold that kind of square clothes?
It feels like it's a square version
And then add pressure
You might be on the side
What kind of board is there on the side?
I guess
Put the clothes on
First of all, the board is curved
And then when I'm imitating him
I'm going to turn it on
Let him hold it up
And then ask if Tim is doing a good job of adjusting the movement
well
I think the basic process is in among the seeds
You can show it on the top
Okay, okay, okay
Okay, ok
You can adjust it
It's so good
Not just easy
It's so easy
Okay
So you said you're going to read it
I use the R-H binding.
I think it's more convenient.
Then I will make a move in C4D
and set a position.
I will set a position.
Then this is a move.
After that, I will export it from the ABC format to MD.
When it goes in, it will keep the D0, which is the t-box.
Then after you finish the costume,
just click on the move model.
Then it will match the costume and the move.
Then you can export it to C4D for material rendering and so on.
And then you can export it to C4D for material rendering.
There is a link to this.
OK!
Thanks!
Look at the question below.
Is there a problem other than Mr. Zhu?
Is there?
It's starting to be dangerous.
Let me check so it's easier to understand.
Is there any other problem?
How did you make the foam on the shoes? I didn't hear you clearly.
Foam on the shoes...
Are you referring to the patterns on the shoes, or the design?
These patterns on the foams are actually created with the C4D.
If you turn up the density, it will look like...
It's a bit like a carousel.
It will look like this.
When I made it, I thought it looked pretty good.
So I didn't put the pattern on the shoes.
I just kept it.
And it turned out like this.
This pattern wasn't made with the stickers.
The pattern was created by itself.
The stickers are just a cutout and a surface color.
I have a question.
How did you create the pattern on your own?
I don't know why.
Normally, you can only create the pattern on the shoes and then create the pattern on the shoes.
You can't create the pattern on your own, right?
So he's asking me.
You can't create the pattern on your own.
Right.
If you don't have the pattern, the pattern won't be able to be created.
But it's an independent model after it's made.
Right.
Or if you want to make it on your own...
If you really want to make it on your own,
you can make the pattern...
No, that's not right.
I wanted to set the transparency to zero.
Then the pattern will disappear in the three-dimensional space.
But I haven't tried it.
And I don't think anyone would want to make the pattern on their own.
You can just take the pattern out and delete it.
Leave a clear pattern.
Yeah.
Oh, I see a pineapple.
Ask MD what software it is.
No, you're here.
And then you don't know what software MD is.
Marvelous Designer is a software that creates three-dimensional clothing with a 2D version.
Through the gravity and the function of the windage in the 3D window,
it can make the 2D version fit in the 3D version,
whether it's a model or your character's assets.
Ah?
Oh.
So it was fake.
Did Mr. Zhu work with foreign clients to translate the English?
If you're emailing to me,
you have the translation software.
But now there are a lot of foreign clients who use WeChat.
If you use WeChat, WeChat has its own translation function.
Yes, yes, we never speak Chinese.
We usually talk in English.
My friend is shy. He wants to ask if Mr. Zhu is single.
Isn't Mr. Zhu...
Oh, that's his girlfriend. He's not married, is he?
I already told him to take off his wife's clothes.
Can he be single?
Oh, I thought you were saying that you are married.
No, I can speak English very well.
I just learned the accent on purpose.
Very, very, very good.
Yes, our MD doesn't support domestic payment.
Pay by WeChat.
Yes, it's updated on the latest website.
Now it's supported by Alipay.
You can buy it.
It used to be very troublesome to buy it.
Yes, now...
You have to use a foreign credit card.
But in fact, we have agents in China.
But now we have Alipay and Alipay on the official website.
So you don't have to find an agent.
There are Alipay and Alipay.
Yes.
And then when I made a bug before,
there was a time when I tested the Alipay,
I found that his payment became six US dollars.
I'm stupid.
Six US dollars a month.
And then I was like,
Oh, there's a bug here.
Hurry up and fix this bug.
Yes.
He has a little more time left because he can't pay this month just like this.
Don't look at me
Alright alright, it's almost time
Alright alright guys, it's almost time, it's time for us to say goodbye
Alright alright alright, it's almost time
I also think Teacher Zhu's work is really great
I'm going to play the game, bye bye
This comment...
This comment is very similar to the one I posted
I'm going to play the game, bye bye
Alright alright
Thank you, thank you
You've worked hard, thank you pineapple rice ball
How did pineapple rice ball become a t-shirt?
What is this?
I just found out that the front says t-shirt
Thank you t-shirt
You should always say thank you
Thank you pineapple rice ball
Thank you
Thank you boss for the rocket or something
Alright alright, it's almost time
My friends, if you have any questions
You can leave a message in the comments below
Or go to Behance or Instagram
To contact Teacher Zhu
No, Teacher Zhu
Teacher Zhu
If you have any questions, feel free to contact me anytime
See you next time